This project is based on the scrollytelling visualization option.

This scrollytelling was created using Vanilla D3 + Scrollama. Please launch it locally using the VSCode Live Server extension, or
other local hosting method.
Alternatively, it can be accessed at https://fnuha.github.io/cs7450hw4/

This visualization was created to communicate the changes in manga over time, both in genre and audience perception/scoring.
It focuses on discussing the demographics of manga, as well as how those demographics have been received by audiences,
and attempts to make sense of the ways that manga demographics have changed over time through pie charts showing distribution,
bar charts and line charts showing scoring per genre and over time, and a scatterplot showing the overall range of scores
in relation to time.

The main feature of this visualization is scrolling. The charts will automatically change as the reader scrolls up and down
the webpage. Minor features include hovering on the pie, bar, and scatterplot charts, along with dataset switching on the scatterplot.